

SUMMARY

Manufacturing technician with more than 10 years of experience planning, developing and implementing factory H&S, Zoning, KPI, HACCP, GMP, CIP, OEE, LOTO, OPL, SOP and Risk Assessement

Currently studying Software Development, with uCertify training course

CONTACT

PHONE: 07548 966 540

E-MAIL: ales.brodnansky@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Programming Piano Guitar Car Driving

CERTIFICATIONS

CIW: Advanced HTML5 and CSS3 Specialist

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
- Using HTML5 API
- Developing HTML5 Forms
- Completing, Submitting and Validating User Input Forms
- Designing for Mobile Devices

MTA: Software Development Fundamentals

- Core Programming
- OOP Programming
- General Software Development
- Web Applications
- Desktop Applications
- Databases

OCA Java SE 8 Programmer OCP Java SE 8 Programmer HACCP Training First Aider Certicate Driving Licence

ALES BRODNANSKY

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Intellectually curious and open-minded, am able to process a lot of information at once. Very much enjoy a challenge, and I'm capable of putting a great deal of energy into a good cause.

EDUCATION

Bussiness Academy Zatec

Sep 2001 to June 2005 Grade of: Economy, Accountancy, Math, IT

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nutricia Liverpool Packing and Manufacturing Technician May 2013 to July 2019

Delivering the Packing plan for my line with the highest levels of service and standards, inline with the SQCDME Key Performance Indicator's, through DaMaWay (an internal process and structure) tools and techniques.

Cains Brewery Manufacturing Technician

May 2011 to May 2013

Providing a comprehensive production service and packing a range of beverages whilst adhering to customer service levels, quality conformance and within budget, in a safe and professional manner.

Greencore Sushi Crosby

March 2009 to Jun 2011

QA Technician - Conducting temperature verification checks, calibration checks and record the results, GMP audits, CCP verification relevant to the area being worked in and report any Non-Conformances through the proper processes, conducting equipment checks, ensure the timely collection of chemical and microbiological samples

SKILLS

- Proficient in all areas of Microsoft Office, including Excel, Word and PowerPoint
- Ability to drive production
- Provide frequent CCP checks and pick up samples
- To be a strong and important part of a production team chain
- Train new staff, sharinng new experiences and SOP knowledge
- Create OPLs
- Calculate daily, weekly, monthly OEE and obtain KPI on regular basis
- Quality Control

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Setting, adjusting and changing over of various production machines.
- Controling and operating machinery within production area
- Basic Java, Csharp, SQL, XML, HTML, CSS3 and JavaScript code reading and writting

LANGUAGES

Bilingual Czech\English, Slovak, Polish